我是奥利弗·奎恩
My name is Oliver Queen.
五年里  我被困在地狱
After 5 years in hell,
我回来只为一个目标
I returned home with only one goal--
拯救我的城市
to save my city,
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
但我之前的方法还不够
but my old approach wasn't enough.
我得成为另一个人
I had to become someone else.
翻译：Silence 肉松
■
我得成为另一个存在
I had to become something else.
我得成为绿箭侠
I had to become the Green Arrow.
翻译：Dzysteven 信徒
《绿箭》前情回顾
Previously on "Arrow"...
你不可能阻止他
You won't be able to stop him.
我们困住他就行
We need to trap him.
翻译：SophiaSaaaga Liv Z小花儿
校对： Michael   肉松  Z小花儿  精校： 陈小圈
爸爸
Dad?
我们是一样的  你和我
We are the same, you and I.
你搞错了
You are wrong.
我跟你完全不同
I am nothing like you.
时间轴 ：风吹来的那片云
我只能杀死他  莱拉
I had to put him down, Lyla.
他想抢我的枪
He had reached for my gun.
特效&后期 ：咖啡Lee     总监：苹果果
艾利克斯  我们在哪
Alex, where are we?
-西娅  -我待不下去了
- Thea. - No. I can't.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
卢比孔河行动
Rubicon,
可以阻止任何国家  包括我国
designed to prevent any country, even our own,
发射核武器
from firing a nuclear missile.
达克撕开皮肤拿走了
Darhk ripped it out.
达克能控制全世界的核武器
Darhk would control the world's nuclear stockpile.
安迪告诉我创世纪即将来临
Andy told me that Genesis was coming.
上帝想重建世界  所以毁掉了世界
God wanted to give the world a do-over, so he destroyed it.
用洪水毁了世界
He destroyed it with a flood.
所以核灭绝就是达克的洪水
So nuclear annihilation is Darhk's flood.
他打算怎么建造他的方舟呢
What's he planning on building as his Ark?
俄罗斯加里宁格勒导弹袭击预警中心
如果这是安东诺夫的恶作剧
汇报
在0316  一至四号导弹仓库已重新启动
正加大供能  进入发射序列
重新启动是什么意思
我无法登陆系统了
弹头已准备就绪
这...
这不是恶作剧
俄罗斯  马尔科维亚  马尔科维亚  我们
Russia, Markovia, Corto Maltese, us,
所有北约组织同盟国
every NATO ally--
卢比孔河行动已掌控了他们所有的核能系统
Rubicon has control over all their nuclear systems.
你是说被蜂巢掌控了
You mean HIVE does.
我知道现在说这话有点晚
I know it's a little late for this,
但不管是谁发明了
but whoever created an algorithm
能重写任何国家核武器的算法
that could override any country's nuclear weapons
这下真的完蛋了
really screwed up.
是阿曼达·沃勒搞出来的
That would be Amanda Waller.
我们还有多少时间
How much time do we have?
我们
We?
奥利弗  我是超能力联合调查组的指挥官
Oliver, I'm the Director of ARGUS,
这已远不是我能决定的了
and this goes way over my head.
这是执政当局的事
This is executive level,
是国防部的事
and this is Department of Defense.
是没错  但还有多少时间
Right, right, right, right, but how much time?
达克还需要一个启动序列
There's a start-up sequence
才能真正的发射核武器
before Darhk can actually launch a nuke.
我们还有不到21小时的时间
We have just under 21 hours.
你必须找到一个能中断序列的办法
You're gonna have to find a way to interrupt that sequence.
卢比孔河行动是核武器大决战的失效保护
Rubicon is a failsafe against nuclear Armageddon.
超能力联合调查组将其设计为绝对无法黑入
ARGUS designed it to be 100% unhackable.
不  她能黑进去  她是最好的
No. She can do it. She's the best.
其实  对卢比孔河行动而言
Well, actually, that would be my father
我父亲才是最佳的人选
as far as Rubicon is concerned.
法国数学家和物理学家
它使用的是傅里叶协议
It uses Fourier protocols.
诺亚基本上就是这方面的专家
Noah practically wrote the book on them.
全世界要面对的是核武器大决战
The world is facing nuclear Armageddon.
我的自尊心以及对我父亲的反感
My pride and my general dislike for my father
在接下来二十几个小时里都不重要了
can take a backseat for the next 20-plus hours.
费利西蒂  这和自尊心无关
Felicity, this isn't about pride.
你父亲是罪犯
Your father's a criminal.
不能相信他
He can't be trusted.
我不是说我们应该相信他
I'm not saying we should trust him.
而是说我们必须相信他
I'm saying we need to.
达克越狱时他也逃出来了
OK. He got out in Darhk's jailbreak.
我们要怎么找他
How do we find him?
我已经在搜索了
I'm already running a search.
你也能联系一下西娅吗
Can you try to get in touch with Thea, too?
谢谢  我们需要她回来
Please. We need her back here.
约翰  能和你说几句吗
John, can I talk to you for a second?
-你怎么样  -不怎么样
- How you doing? - Been better.
我不会假装
Well, I'm not gonna pretend
理解你的痛苦
to understand what you're going through.
奥利弗  你母亲去世时你也经历过
Well, Oliver, you've been through this with your mother,
所以我不太明白
which is why I can't quite understand
你为什么把整个世界的命运
why you're putting the fate of the world
交到另一个邪恶家长的身上
in the hands of another evil parent.
我并不是相信库特勒
I'm not trusting Kuttler.
我相信的是费利西蒂
I trust Felicity,
我们应该让她做她擅长的事
and we should just let her do her job, OK?
我们也有自己的任务
We have one of our own.
对  阻止达克
Yeah, stopping Darhk.
他的魔力来自死亡
His magic is powered by death,
所以就算其中一个核武器袭击成功
so if even one of those nukes hits--
他就所向无敌了
He will be unstoppable.
好吧  那你有什么计划
OK. What's your play?
如果他打算利用这些死亡事件
Well, if he is planning on harnessing all of this death,
他应该会待在结点室
he's gonna be in something called a nexus chamber.
大致说来  那是魔力收集者
Basically, it's a collector magic.
我还以为地震机器
And here I thought earthquake machines
已经够奇怪的了
were as strange as it got.
伊斯林·福尔图娜告诉我其中一个房间
Esrin Fortuna told me that one of these chambers
就在星城
exists in Star City.
我猜它坐落在地脉
I'm betting it falls on a ley line.
雌狐是怎么说的  魔力无线网络
What did Vixen call them-- Wi-Fi for magic?
-没错  -这座城市很大  奥利弗
- Yeah. - It's a big city, Oliver.
我们只有21个小时
We got 21 hours.
一步步来
One step at a time.
我们必须帮他们
We have to help them!
我们会帮这些人的
We're gonna help these people!
你在找什么
What are you looking for?
瑞特的人在岛上找到了出路
Reiter's men found a way on the island.
肯定有出路的
There has to be a way off.
岛的东面有架飞机
There's a plane east end of the island,
离这很远
And it's far.
我们能赶到的
We'll make it.
那是什么
What's that?
也许是一种求救方式
This may be a way to call for help.
我们走
Let's go!
然后是
And...
狗叫
Woof.
我知道
I know.
可以预料是这个设计的严重缺陷
The predictability was a terrible flaw in the design.
可以预料也是你的缺陷
Predictability is your flaw, too.
每次我的生活开始变糟  你就会出现了
Every time my life starts to suck, you show up.
下去吧
Leave us.
那只手是你新哥儿们的礼物吗
Is that hand a present from your new best friend?
我这么做不是为了假肢  西娅
I'm not doing this for a prosthetic, Thea.
-我是为了保护你  -保护我
- I'm doing it to keep you safe. - Keep me safe.
-没错  保护你  -是吧
- Yes. Keep you safe. - Yeah.
我说过  可以预料
Like I said, predictable.
我唯一不懂的是
Only thing I don't get is how is brainwashing
洗脑我真心喜欢的人算什么保护我
some guy I really like in your plan to keep me safe?
他那样不怪我
His conditioning wasn't my idea.
鲁维·达克希望在最后阶段
Ruvé Darhk wanted to ensure his compliance
确保他的忠诚
in the final phase.
什么的最后阶段
Final phase of what?
叫什么创世纪
Something called Genesis.
达克计划用核弹夷平全世界
Darhk plans to burn the world in a nuclear fire
而我们在这里很安全
while we are protected down here.
天啊
Oh, god.
然后他和他的随从就能重建
Then he and his followers can rebuild.
说实话  这和我以前
Truth be told, it's not dissimilar
针对贫民窟的计划  没什么两样
to the plan I had for the Glades once upon a time,
但规模大得多
but on a much, much larger scale.
我想  你觉得
Let me guess-- you don't think
毁灭整个世界完全不疯狂
that destroying the entire world is completely insane?
这个世界才疯狂
The world is what's insane.
已经无药可救
It is beyond saving.
世界需要重建改写
It needs a do-over, a reset.
听着  一旦认识到达克的计划是必然的
Look. Once I realized Darhk's plan was inevitable,
就很容易取舍了
the math was simple.
你自救[省省]吧
Save yourself.
还有我女儿...
And my daughter...
虽然她不想被救
even if she doesn't want to be saved.
我已经完全懒得告诉你
Look. I am way, way past the point of telling you
你疯了
that you are crazy.
我只想见艾利克斯
I just want to see Alex.
我只想知道他没事
I just want to know he's ok,
我也明白
And look, I--I get it.
我困在这儿了
I'm stuck here,
但我可以在这里规规矩矩的
but I can be stuck here and compliant,
也可以搅得你们鸡犬不宁
or I can be a pain in your ass,
立刻带我去见他
So take me to him now.
-好啊  亲爱的  -好啊
- Hey, hon. - Hi.
怎么了
What's up?
我今早在你家...
When I was at your place this morning, I, um...
发现了这个
I found this.
你翻我的东西干什么
What are you doing going through my stuff?
瞄一眼
Snooping.
但  但这与你无关  唐娜
But--but--but this isn't any of your business, Donna.
不  亲爱的  其实与我有关
No, no, babe. It is my business actually,
你要被停职了
you getting suspended.
算是吧
It is kind of.
唐娜
Donna.
这是什么
What is this?
这是  这是一份证词
It's--it's, um-- it's an affidavit.
派克说如果我签上名
Pike said if I put my name to it,
我就能拿回警徽
then--then I get my badge back.
上面说你不知道劳蕾尔是黑金丝雀
It says you didn't know that Laurel was the Black Canary.
我可能进不了曼萨俱乐部
I may not be in Mansa,
实为门萨俱乐部  高智商人群才有资格加入的俱乐部
但我识字  亲爱的
but I know how to read, sweetie.
应该是门萨俱乐部
I think it's Mensa actually.
你跟我说你知道劳蕾尔在做这个
You told me that you knew what Laurel was doing.
-没错  -是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
所以你说谎了
So this is a lie.
是的  但这事很复杂
Yeah, but it's a complicated lie.
-是吗  -是的
- Is it? - Yeah.
是的
Yeah.
因为派克说
Because according to Pike,
内务部打算另外调查
IAB are willing to look the other way
我和达克的合作  而我其实是
about my working with Darhk because I was...
为了保护劳蕾尔
protecting Laurel.
如果她是超级英雄  还需要你保护她吗
Why would you have to protect her if she was a superhero?
没错  正是如此  你懂了
Yeah, exactly. Now you see.
我只懂他们要你说谎
I see that they're asking you to lie.
亲爱的  算了吧
Sweetheart, come on.
我只想当个警察
All I ever wanted was to--was to be a cop,
如果说些小谎话
and what's a small lie if
能让我为这座城市做更多贡献呢
it means I can do some good for this city?
不  不  是这样的
No. No. That's just it.
谎话没有大小之分  亲爱的
There aren't any small lies, hon.
和骗子生过孩子的女人
Take it from someone who had a child
悟出的道理
with a man who was a liar.
我不是诺亚·库特勒
I'm not Noah Kuttler.
我知道  亲爱的  所以我爱你
I know, honey, and that's why I love you.
好吗
Ok?
我爱你
I love you...
所以我相信
And that's why I have faith that...
你会做出正确的选择
you're gonna do the right thing.
先生们  有些小差事需要你们跑腿
Gentlemen, I have a little errand I need you to run,
解决一些遗留问题
a loose end that needs tying up,
类似于...
Not unlike...
我感受到一丝不情愿啊  布里克先生
Do I detect some obstinacy, Mr. Brick?
我以前是发命的  达克  而不是受命的
I'm used to giving the orders, Darhk, not taking them.
我把你救出
Not even as a little
铁山监狱  你都不谢我吗
thank-you for busting you out of Iron Heights?
感恩的心哪里去了
Whatever happened to gratitude?
我过来了  不是吗
I'm here, ain't I?
当全世界都在核爆炸的
And when the whole world
蘑菇云中倍受煎熬
is sitting under a field of mushroom clouds,
你们会很庆幸来了这里
You will be glad that you are.
回到任务上来
Now then, back to the errand.
你们有人听说过计算者吗
Have either of you boys heard of the Calculator?
这里没人
There's no one here.
我发现了多态加密的
I found a deep-trunk fiber optic hookup
深层光纤连接
with polymorphic encryption.
诺亚一定在那里  相信我
Noah is there, trust me.
她说得没错  你看
I think she's right. Look.
装配那东西的人不喜欢意外
Whoever rigged that up didn't want to be surprised.
我在追踪蓝牙信号
I'm tracing the bluetooth signal.
朝西南方走
Head southwest.
好吧  他不在
Well, he's not here.
他应该在
He has to be.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
他之前在
He was.
他好像匆匆逃离了
Looks like he bolted and in a hurry.
逃离谁
Bolted from whom?
录像是20分钟前的
This was 20 minutes ago.
看来从铁山监狱越狱的不只有库特勒
Looks like Kuttler wasn't the only one that left Iron Heights.
那些跟他一起的是幽灵
Those are ghosts with him.
蜂巢抓我父亲要做什么
What does HIVE want with my father?
好了  给我找到那个干瘦蠢货
Ok. Find that scrawny son of a bitch,
你们找到后  干掉他
And when you do, kill him.
欢迎来到诺亚方舟
Welcome to Tevat Noah,
你们新时代的家
your home in the new era.
请前往报到大楼
Please proceed to the registration building
获取给你们分配的住宅
to receive your residence assignments.
抱歉了
Sorry about that.
找到这里可真不容易
It wasn't easy finding my way down here.
你们幽灵保守秘密是一把好手
You ghosts are swell at keeping secrets
但忍受酷刑可没那么厉害
but less swell resisting torture,
所以你不如给我省点麻烦
So why don't you spare me the trouble
直接告诉我达米恩·达克在哪
and tell me where I can find Damien Darhk?
绿   箭
第四季  第二十一集
你说得没错
You're right.
只有库特勒能阻止卢比孔河行动
Kuttler's the only one that can stop Rubicon.
所以达克想置他于死地
That's why Darhk wanted him dead.
你还好吗
You all right?
还好  只是想到了世界上的冲突
Yeah. The word conflicted comes to mind.
最起码我们知道他逃走了
Well, at least we know he got away.
但不算是开了个好头
But not much of a head start.
我黑进了库特勒的服务器
I hacked Kuttler's server to see if there was
看能不能找到他去向的信息
anything in there that could point us to where he would run to,
不过他清空了所有缓存
and he cleared the cache,
所以我没法恢复任何文件
so I can't recover any files,
但里面有个叫渡鸦之刺的根目录
But there is a root directory called Ravenspur.
渡鸦之刺是什么
What's Ravenspur?
不知道  但听起来很耳熟
Don't know. Does sound familiar.
我只是不知道为什么
I just don't know why.
我们没多少时间了
We're running out of time.
全世界都没时间了  所以是啊
The whole world is, so yeah.
与此同时  我的地脉算法找出了
Meantime, my ley line algorithm kicked back
有20%的可能是达克魔力俱乐部的地方
a possible twenty on a magical clubhouse for Darhk.
我们赶走了其中一些人
We drove some of them off,
但瑞特正在派增援过来
but Reiter's sending reinforcements.
瑞特死了
Reiter's dead.
我们在无线电里听到他了
We heard him on the radio.
他还活着
He's alive.
包里有一张岛上的地图
There's a map of the island in the pack.
带他们到飞机那里去
Get them to the plane.
那你呢
What about you?
我去找瑞特
I'm gonna find Reiter,
然后结束这一切
and I'm gonna end this.
那我也留下来
Then I'm staying, too.
你还记得你告诉我的话吗
Do you remember what you told me?
只有怪兽才能杀死另一只怪兽
It takes a monster to kill a monster.
现在带这些人回家
Now get these people home.
费利西蒂刚打电话过来
Felicity just called.
她有点事要见我
She needs to see me about something.
一切都还好吗
Is everything all right?
我不知道  因为是费利西蒂
I don't know. It's felicity,
所以  你知道的  难说
So, you know, you never know.
你要签那份文件了吗
Were you signing that thing?
是的  正准备签
Yeah, I was about to.
在你冲我翻白眼之前
Before you give me that dirty look,
你可能想先读读这份文件
you might want to, uh, read this thing.
我已经读过了
I already read it.
就读一下  拜托了
Just read it, please.
这看起来
It's looks a--
是啊  有点不一样了
Yeah, it's a little different, huh?
"虽然我一开始并不同意
"Although I was against at first,
但我看到劳蕾尔作为黑金丝雀
I came to see what Laurel was doing
所做的
was vital...
都是必不可少
and important and good
至关重要的好事"
as the Black Canary."
我稍微修改了一下
I gave it a little rewrite.
宝贝
Baby.
我真为你感到骄傲
I am so proud of you.
劳蕾尔也会的
Laurel would be, too.
我签这个是在葬送我自己的职位
This is me signing my badge away.
不  你还不能确定
No. You don't know that.
你能确定的是
All you can know for sure
你在做正确的事
is that you're doing the right thing.
丹尼斯先生
Mr. Dennis.
斯莫克小姐
Ms. Smoak.
你一直没回我电话
You haven't returned my calls.
是的  不好意思  一直很忙
Yes, I am sorry. I've been busy.
我也很忙
So have I.
忙着为你管理公司
Running your company.
需要我提醒你对于帕尔默科技
Do I need to remind you of your responsibilities
所肩负的责任吗
to Palmer Tech?
不  不需要  但你一定要相信我
No, you don't, but you're just gonna have to believe me
我现在手上的事情
when I tell you that what is on my plate right now
重要得多
is much more important.
我应该过会再来吗
Should I come back?
不  不用  别走
No, no. Please stay.
斯莫克小姐  董事会
Miss smoak, the board--
可以等着
Can wait.
不管是何事如此重要  但愿是值得的
Whatever's so important, I hope it's worth it.
你好  领带不错  非常...尴尬
Hi. I like your tie. It's very--awkward.
谢谢你能见我
Thank you for meeting me.
当然了  我的宝贝女儿
Of course, my baby girl.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
你在开玩笑吗  我会一直在你身边
Are you kidding? I'm always here for you.
只要周围没有蜂群
As long as there's no bees around.
没有蜂群
No bees.
怎么了  你还好吗
What--are you ok?
渡鸦之刺这个词你有印象吗
Does the word Ravenspur mean anything to you?
如果这和你爸爸有关  甜心
If this is something to do with your father, honey--
看来有印象  我记得你俩谈论过这个
So it does. I remember the two of you talking about it.
不仅仅是谈论  那是我们之前
Not just talk. It's a--it's a cabin
喜欢去的一间位于柏树湾的小屋
in Cypress Cove we used to like to go to.
你知道的  我们会品着红酒
We'd, you know--we'd nurse a bottle of wine,
听着莱昂纳尔·里奇的歌做爱
make love to Lionel Richie.
我是他的小爱人
I was his penny lover.
你知道吗  你爸爸
You know, your father
能持续一整晚
could go all night long.
好了  够了  我不
Ok. That's enough. I don't--
你知道吗  其实我想我就是在
You know what? Actually, I think you were conceived
渡鸦之刺怀上你的
in Ravenspur.
求你了别说了  求你了
Please make it stop, please.
不  认真的  甜心  我认真和你说
No. Seriously, honey. I want to be serious for a minute.
如果有什么事和你爸有丁点儿关系...
If this is anything remotely to do with your father--
别担心  我能处理好
Don't worry. I have it handled.
我要不是因为担心你
I wouldn't be a Jewish mother
也不会这么唠叨
if I didn't worry.
宝贝  这是干什么
Baby, what's that for?
但愿你永远都不必知道
With any luck you'll never have to find out.
这儿什么都没有
There's nothing here.
怎么  还想让他立个牌子吗
What, you think he was gonna put up a sign?
我在想会不会是一个
I was thinking more along the lines
带着自动武器的幽灵
of ghosts with automatic weapons.
或许我们该穿工作服来
Maybe we should have brought our work clothes.
我能和你说件事吗
Can I talk to you about something?
-说吧  -我和莱拉谈过了
- Yeah. - I spoke to Lyla.
她很担心你
She's worried about you because
因为你说出于自卫朝安迪开了枪
you said that you shot Andy in self-defense.
奥利弗  我不想谈这件事
Oliver I don't want to talk about this.
你从没和我说过自卫的事  约翰
You just never said anything about self-defense to me, John.
我不能告诉莱拉真相
Couldn't tell Lyla the truth
然后让她再那样看待我
and have her look at me the same way anymore.
别这样  你又不知道
Come on. You don't know that.
奥利弗  你是这世上最了解
Oliver, you're the last person on earth to lecture
为什么要对爱人说谎的人
someone about lying to the people they love.
我不是在对你说教
I'm not lecturing.
我只是担心
I'm worried.
这方面你比我强得多
You're better than me at this,
我从来没见过你如此受伤
and you're hurting worse than I have ever seen you.
对你妻子说谎只会让事情更糟
Don't compound that by lying to your wife.
我对费利西蒂说谎
The fact that I lied to Felicity does not
没有降低这话的可信度
give me less credibility.
要说的话  只能说
If anything, it should tell you
我知道自己在说什么
that I know what I'm talking about.
-在  -诺亚在赛普拉斯湾的一个小屋里
- Yeah. -Noah's at a cabin in Cypress Cove.
交给我们
We got him.
这就过去
We're on our way.
你真难找啊  库特勒
You're a hard man to find, Kuttler.
出来吧  我们不会让你痛苦的
Come out now. We'll make it painless.
帮我们搞定  不然要你好看
Make us work for it, we'll make it last.
最讨厌别人逃了
I hate it when they run.
你再让我追
You make me chase you anymore,
我就要开枪了
I'm gonna put a bullet in you.
计划不就是如此吗
Isn't that the plan?
给你个公平的机会
I'm willing to give you a sporting chance.
我在牢里就听过这个游戏了  布里克先生
I heard about this game while I was in prison, Mr. Brick.
打倒你  就放我走
You let me walk if I take you down.
达克说你是个聪明人
Darhk said you was a smart bloke.
你觉得呢
So what do you say?
这就是世界末日了
It's the end of the world as I understand it.
别傻站在这儿  上来
Don't just stand there. Get in!
接到他了
I got him.
斯巴达  撤
Spartan, fall back!
简单地说
Let's make this simple.
这不是和解
This isn't a reconciliation,
也不是团聚
this isn't a reunion.
是你要帮我拯救世界
This is you helping me save the world.
你为什么觉得我帮得了
And what makes you think I can?
达米恩·达克觉得你行
Damien Darhk thinks you can.
所以他才派了去年的最佳杀手
That's why he sent last year's greatest hits
去抓你
to take you down.
你是个聪明人  我猜你知道卢比孔河行动
You're a smart man. I'm assuming you know what Rubicon is.
我猜它已经被达克先生控制了
And I'm assuming it's under Mr. Darhk's control.
我们有12小时来阻止他
We have 12 hours to stop it.
就这样
That's it?
你似乎很惊讶
You seem surprised.
我以为要讨价还价
I was expecting a quid pro quo.
费利西蒂  我或许是个糟糕的父亲
Felicity I may be a terrible father.
或许
May?
但我不是禽兽
But I'm not a monster.
糟不糟糕  我都是你父亲
Terrible or not, I am your father.
只要你还活着
As long as you live in it,
我就不希望这个世界毁灭
I have an interest in seeing that this world doesn't end.
即便如此  我确实需要些东西
That said, I do need something.
一点都不意外
Color me shocked.
我用这台机器黑不进卢比孔河行动
I can't hack Rubicon with this setup,
时间不够
not in the time we have.
我需要你在帕尔默科技发明的
I'm going to need the quantum subluminal processor
光束量子处理器
you developed at Palmer Tech.
你怎么知道我们...
How did you even know that we...
天  你该不会是想利用这个时机
God help me if you are using the end of days
继续从我公司偷东西吧
to steal from my company again.
虽然我很擅长同时处理多个任务
I'm an excellent multitasker,
但这次你可以相信我
but you can trust me this time.
帕尔默科技
斯莫克小姐
Ms. Smoak.
丹尼斯先生
Mr. Dennis.
你一定是太想让我和董事会谈话
You must be very desperate for me to talk to the board
保安都用上了
since you brought security to dragoon me.
他们不是带你去会议室的
These men are not here to take you to the conference room.
他们是来护送你出去的
They're here to escort you out of the building.
什么意思
Excuse me?
董事会非常担心  你想要放弃
The board has grave concerns about your plans
可植入生物刺激素的决定
to basically give away the biostimulant implant.
他们想和你讨论相关事宜
They wanted to discuss the matter with you.
我会和他们谈的
And I will talk to them.
太晚了
It's too late for that.
他们投票决定将你革职
They voted to terminate you
立即生效
effective immediately.
我只是拿点东西
Well I just need to grab something,
我会自己出去的  谢谢
and I will show myself out, thank you.
抱歉  实验室的一切都是公司财产
I'm sorry, but everything in this lab is proprietary.
我们不能让你带走公司财产
We cannot allow you to leave with company property.
什么  你在开玩笑吧
Excuse me? You have to be kidding.
我很抱歉
I'm very sorry.
我也不希望是这样的结局
I had hoped that this would end differently.
好了各位  你们就搬到这里
All right, folks. You're just moving right on in here.
祝一天愉快
Have a great day.
艾利克斯
Alex?
你刚才像疯了一样跑开
Hey, you. You ran off like a crazy person.
感觉好些了吗
Are you feeling better?
你知道这里发生了什么吗
Do you know what's going on here?
知道  瑞文告诉我了
Yeah. Ruve told me.
长官  有情况
Sir, we have a situation.
是不是很棒
Isn't it fantastic?
一点都不
It is not fantastic.
这是世界末日
It's the end of the world.
不  只是开启新的纪元
No. It's just the beginning of a new one.
我去从政  希望做一些改变
I got into politics to make a difference, right,
让世界变得更好
to make the world a better place,
瑞文让我看到了唯一的办法
and Ruve has shown me that the only way to do that
就是重新开始
is to start over.
听我说
Just listen to me.
你现在受到了
You are under the influence
某种药物的影响
of some type of drug right now,
我们需要离开这里
and we need to get out of here.
你要相信我  好吗
You're just gonna have to trust me, ok?
晚点再让他相信你
He can trust you later.
朗尼·马尚在这
Lonnie Machin is here.
就我们所知  已经有五个达米恩的手下
He's killed 5 of Damien's men
被他杀了
that we know about.
对这事我可以有很多种回答
There's plenty of ways I can respond to that,
我还是想说  真棒
but I'm gonna go with good.
核武器会让空气变得不宜吸入
He's hitting the co2 scrubbers hours
他计划在此前数小时
before nuclear weapons will render
破坏二氧化碳洗涤装置
the atmoathere above us unbreathable.
如果方舟的生命支持系统损坏
If the Ark's life support fails,
我们都会窒息而死
we all suffocate.
朗尼·马尚是谁
Who's Lonnie Machin?
是西娅的某位前男友
He's kind of an ex-boyfriend of Thea's.
达米恩跟我说了你俩的特殊关系
Damien told me about your special connection to him.
我需要你帮我把他抓回监狱
I need you to help me put him back in the box,
否则我们都得死
or we're all dead.
你还好吗  到手了吗
You all right? Did you get it?
还没拿到处理器就被炒了鱿鱼
I got fired before I could take the processor.
我甚至不能露脸
I can't even show my face in there.
或许我们应该报警说有炸弹恐吓
Maybe we should call in a bomb threat,
清空大楼
just empty the place,
或者真的放个炸弹
or maybe plant an actual bomb.
放个小小的  不会伤人的那种
Just a small one, one that doesn't hurt anybody,
但我们得...
but we have to--
或许我们应该直接走进去
Maybe we should just go in.
光天化日的  穿着装备
It's too risky to wear the gear
风险太大
in the daylight.
旧基地的电梯能用吗
What about the elevator at the old lair?
拉万事件之后
Mr. Dennis shut it down
丹尼斯先生就把它关了
after the Larvan attack.
那么约翰是对的  我们就直接进去
So John's right. We'll go in
帮你和你父亲把它偷出来  那东西在...
and help you and your father boost it from--
柯蒂斯的实验室
It's in Curtis' lab.
你想让我帮我父亲偷我自己的东西
You want me to help my father steal from me?
严格来说已经不是你的了  对吧
Well, it's not exactly yours anymore, is it?
对  好像确实是
Nope. Guess not.
门打开了
Door's unlocked.
你们数到三就进来
Give me a count of 3 and then come on in.
收到
Copy that.
我喜欢这个计策
I love all this subterfuge.
我们的守护天使是绿箭侠吗
Might our guardian angel be the Green Arrow?
预算上明明列出来了
This was a line item on the budget list,
但到现在都没修好
and it's still not fixed,
他们还敢炒我鱿鱼
and they have the gall to fire me.
挺有意思的  我们俩合作
This is fun, working together.
我把话说清楚了
Let's make this clear.
这不是父女间的亲子游戏
This is not a father-daughter bonding exercise.
费利西蒂  有工作人员经过你那层
Felicity, we have personnel walking the floor.
听我指令行动
You might want to just go on my signal.
收到
Copy that.
听着  我知道自己做过许多
Look. I know I've done what appears
可怕的事情
to be some terrible things.
你想偷我东西
You tried to steal from me.
我们现在不就在偷你东西吗
Are we not stealing from you now?
不  首先  公司已经不属于我
No. "A," it's not my company anymore,
其次  我们是在拯救地球
and "B," we're trying to save the world.
我不是说了等我指令吗
Didn't I say go on my signal?
好
OK.
就现在
Now.
我擅长解决二元的问题
I'm good at solving binary problems,
但揣摩内心...
but matters of the heart--
不是你的强项  并且
Are not your forte, and stealing a processor
偷处理器拯救地球的时候
to save the end of the world
并不适合讲这些
is not the right time for this conversation.
其实  我总是告诉自己
On some level, I've always told myself
我不知道如何做父亲
I just didn't know how to be a father
或是丈夫
or a husband.
作为一个聪明人  你好像不明白
And for a smart guy, you don't seem to understand
什么叫做合适的时间
the concept of not the right time.
我不知道自己为何窃取你公司的科技成果
I don't know why I tried to steal your company's tech.
因为习惯吧  我猜  或者是更深层的原因
Habit, I suppose, or something deeper.
天哪  那个狗杂种
Gah! That son of a bitch!
我被炒了才45分钟
I've been fired for, like, 45 minutes,
他就已经取消了我的权限
and he's already locked me out.
你有电磁波发生器
You have an electromagnetic wave generator
和电池保养器吗
and battery tender?
就能强制重启了
To force the restart.
有
Yes.
太好了
Yes!
芝麻开门
Open sesame.
通过权限
帕默科技
好了
That's it.
伙计们  东北面楼梯有人来了
Guys, I've got incoming, northeast stairwell.
交给我
On it.
还有子锁
It's under a sublock.
弹不出来  从没发生过这事  除非...
It won't eject. That never happens unless...
这个  拿不到处理器我们不能走
That. We can't leave without the processor.
-复制一个就行了  -你的监听装置
- We can if we clone it. - Your sniffer device.
我们可以无线复制处理器操作码
We can copy the processor's operating code wirelessly.
更多人上来了
More movement.
费利西蒂  你一定是触发了什么装置
Felicity, you must have tripped something
现在保安都往实验室方向去了
because I have security coming to the lab right now.
我们快没时间了
We're running out of time.
复制还没完成
The device isn't finished.
-快点  -就快好了
- Come on. - It's almost there.
快啊
Come on.
费利西蒂  你得赶快离开那儿
Felicity, you have to get out of there.
保安已经进去了
Security's inbound.
研发实验室安全
The R&D lab is secure.
听说你们需要搭个便车
I heard you needed a lift.
你就是当初抓我的人
You're the one who arrested me.
他今天不抓你
He's not doing that now.
拿到了吗
You get it?
没有
No.
情况有多糟
How bad is it?
库特勒复制了处理器的90%
Kuttler was able to clone 90% of the processor.
他或许能推算出剩下的10%
He may be able to extrapolate the remaining 10%
做出一个可运行的处理器
to build us a workable processor.
我拿些零件给他
I'm gathering parts for him to work with,
但我们还是需要上传重写的代码
but we're still gonna need to upload the override codes
到每一个核弹发射井
to every nuke silo individually.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
只能通过服务器集群
Only from a Server Farm.
奎恩先生
Mr. Queen!
我的手下在森林里寻找我的财产
My men are searching the woods for my property,
但你选择不跟他们共同赴死
but you chose not to die with them.
我杀了几个掉队的
I killed a few of the stragglers.
我的能力已经超越你的想象
My power has grown beyond your imagining.
让我展示给你看
Let me show you.
你很勇敢  奎恩先生
Valiant effort, Mr. Queen,
但仍难免一死
but still only mortal.
主洗涤装置就在这里
The primary scrubber's in here.
我敢说马尚也在这里
I'm betting Machin is, too.
难道让我赤手空拳跟他打吗
Well, don't I get something to fight him with?
出于某种原因  我无法放心
I don't think I can trust you with a weapon
让你使用武器
for some reason.
恐怕你就只能
You're just gonna have to make do
使用格斗术来对付他
with Krav Maga, I'm afraid.
真是讽刺
Oh, the irony.
达克所有的寄生虫都住在地下
All Darhk's parasites living underground,
呼吸着这些烂泥排放出来的废气
breathing the waste product of sludge.
如果我把这个打开会怎么样
What happens if I turn this dial?
如果你们不肯告诉我
Well, if you're not gonna tell me,
那我只能自己来挖掘真相了
I'm just gonna have to see for myself.
别碰那东西
Step away from that.
快离开  小姑娘
Run along, little girl.
我现在正忙着
I'm a tad busy at the moment
准备杀掉所有的人
trying to kill everyone here.
我不是什么小姑娘  朗尼
I'm not a little girl, Lonnie.
还记得我吗
Remember me?
我叫西娅·奎恩
My name is Thea Queen.
是我把你的脸弄成这样的
I'm the one that gave you that face.
老天
Mommy.
你不穿红皮衣我都没认出你
I didn't recognize you without the red leather.
你来这干什么
Whatever are you doing here?
我明白  达克欺骗了你
Look. I get it. You're mad at Darhk
你对他恼羞成怒
because he screwed you over,
现在你想报复他
and now you trying to get pay back.
我不是来阻止你的
I'm not gonna stop you. Ok?
其实我是来帮你的
If anything, I'm gonna help you.
但这里都是些无辜的人
But there are innocent people here,
他们被洗脑了
people that have been brainwashed,
他们并不该死
and they don't deserve to die.
朗尼  别这样做
Lonnie, don't do this.
我会帮你扳倒达克的  好吗
I will help you take down Darhk, ok?
我们可以联手对付他
We can do this together.
你得赶紧离开这里
You just need to get out of here.
你为什么要这样做
What the hell did you do that for?
我快劝服他了
I had him.
不  你并没有
No, you didn't.
炸弹启动了
Explosive charges.
无论你说什么
He was gonna blow the scrubber
他都会炸毁设备
no matter what you said.
你能拆除吗
Can you disarm it?
很快就会知道了
We'll soon find out.
星城数据交换中心
安全
Clear!
我需要子节点来使服务器脱机
I'm gonna need the subnode taken offline.
好  我办得到
Ok. I can do that.
我来掩护他
I'll cover him.
我会照顾好他的
I'll take care of him.
去工作吧
Get to work.
认识你很高兴
Nice to meet you.
我女儿还真是有些厉害的朋友
My daughter certainly has some very impressive friends.
需要多长时间
How long is this gonna take?
理论上说  会赶在达克摧毁世界前完成
Ideally, less than it takes Mr. Darhk to nuke the world.
我并不是我女儿心目中的那种人  知道吗
I'm not the man my daughter thinks, you know?
别跟我说  跟她说
Don't tell me. Tell her.
我试过了
I've tried.
我试过向她解释我的双重身份
I tried explaining that there are two sides to me,
父亲和黑客
the father and the hacker.
她就只看到我作为罪犯的一面
She sees only the criminal.
我跟你说这些是因为我觉得
I mention this because you strike me as someone
你就是过着双重生活的人
with experience leading a dual life.
能跟我分享点心得吗
Any insights you'd care to share?
心得就是  这不管用
Yeah. It doesn't work.
你失去她就是因为活在两种不同的人生中
You leading a dual life is why you lost her.
听起来这是你的个人经验
You sound like you're talking from some personal experience.
怎么回事
What's that?
费利西蒂使服务器脱机了
Felicity's taken the subnode offline,
不过又有了个新的问题
and we've developed a new problem.
-什么问题  -卢比孔河行动密码里有蠕虫病毒
- What? - Tapeworm in the Rubicon code,
反侵袭了你在蜂巢的朋友
antihack failsafe courtesy
好心设置的故障保护
of your friends in HIVE.
-你能解决吗  -我解决了
- Can you override it? - I just did
不过蠕虫病毒已经先我一步
but not before the tapeworm transmitted
传输了这个终端的位置
this terminal's location.
我们大概有90秒的时间
Figure we have about 90 seconds.
-90秒后呢  -蜂巢会把我们所有人
- Until what? ?- Till HIVE rains all manner?
都送往地狱
of hell down on us.
发生什么事了
What happened?
蜂巢知道我们的位置了
HIVE has our position.
他们来之前我们大概有一分钟时间
We have maybe a minute before they arrive.
他们正在设法阻止我
They're working on shutting me down,
不过我有点小伎俩
but I know a few tricks.
我们俩联手会快上一倍
This will go twice as fast with the two of us.
我们会尽量拖住他们的
We'll hold them off as long as we can.
建立防御带
Establish a perimeter.
格杀勿论
Shoot to kill.
我无需告诉你们其中缘由
I don't need to tell you what's riding on this.
总统和国防部长命我们进入二级战备
POTUS and SECDEF have taken us to Defcon-2.
才二级  他们可真乐观
Just two? They're optimistic.
他们不想造成民众恐慌
They don't want to cause a panic.
总统问我是否可以将全世界的命运
The president asked me if the fate of the world
托付在一个IT女
is resting the hands of an I.T. girl,
一名罪犯和两个身穿万圣节服装的人手上
a criminal, and two guys in Halloween costumes.
这可不是什么万圣节服装
They're not Halloween costumes.
去拿神像
Get the idol!
我们得走了
We got to go!
瑞特怎么办
What about Reiter?
没有神像  他什么也做不了
He can't do anything without the idol.
快跑
Come on!
如果此刻就是世界末日
If this is the end of the world,
我觉得这样也不错
I don't mind going out like this.
能不能别说了
Don't you ever stop?
跟我女儿说起来就没完
Not when it comes to my daughter, no.
艾利克斯  没事了
Alex? Everything's fine.
我们拆除了所有炸药
We took out all the explosives.
艾利克斯
Al--alex?
艾利克斯  老天  你...
Alex, oh, god. Oh, god. Are you--
没事  挺好  好极了
Fine? Ok? Hunky dory?
相信我  再次搅乱
Believe me, there is nothing
别人的复仇计划
hunky dory about screwing up someone's
真是糟透了
plan for vengeance a second time,
这样一来我就得在这候着达克先生
which means I've got to wait for Mr. Darhk to arrive
然后执行备用计划
and go with plan B.
可以说  我就有时间大开杀戒了
It's left me with some time to kill, so to speak.
好吧  艾利克斯  醒醒
Ok. Alex, come on.
放心  他没事
Relax. He's fine.
只是晕一会儿
Just taking a little nap.
你这是怎么了
What is it with you?
你为什么总是对某些人
Why are you always at the mercy
如此仁慈
of some guy?
你可以自己做决定  西娅
You can make your own decisions, Thea.
你不是枚棋子
You're not a pawn.
你是女王
You're a queen.
懂吗
Get it?
对  对  我懂
Yeah. Yeah, I get it.
他们来了
Here they come.
这火力够大的
That's a lot of firepower.
我们不必干掉他们
We don't need to beat them.
我们只需为费莉西蒂父女俩争取足够时间
We just need to buy Felicity and her father enough time.
西娅
Thea?
艾利克斯  快离开这
Alex, get out of here!
别动他
Get away from him!
我这是在解放你  圣母
I'm liberating you, mommy!
你不必再让人蒙蔽你的思想
You don't need another man clouding your mind.
艾利克斯  跑
Alex, run!
不
No!
艾利克斯
Alex!
对不起
I'm sorry.
我想我找到了300条上行传输线路的算法
I think I got an algorithm down to 300 lines for the uplink.
你试过破解干扰状态信息密码吗
Have you tried to break the JSI encryption ?
那样就能直接绕过可编程阵列程序
That way, you can directly bypass the PAL.
对  没错
Yeah, you're right.
卢比孔河行动三分钟后发射核武器
3 minutes till Rubicon launches the nukes.
守望者  阿玛尔朝里面去了
Overwatch, Amar is headed inside.
我们要没时间了
We're running out of time.
-你受伤了吗  -没有
- Are you hit? - No!
不  不  不
No, no, no, no.
不
Oh, no.
怎么了
What's happening?
核武器都搞定了
We got every nuke
唯独漏了一个
except one.
怎么回事
RDS-37刚启动了发射编列
朝美国境内发射了
漏掉了一枚  已经发射了
We lost one. It's in the air.
目标直指市政局纪念厅
Headed straight for Monument Point.
子弹射穿了  但你得忍住别动
The bullet went through, but I need you to hold still.
有更重要的事需要咱们担心
I think we have more important concerns,
比如防止再发射一枚核弹
such as preventing another launch.
我以为你俩阻止了卢比孔河行动
I thought you two stopped Rubicon.
卢比孔河行动知道导弹没有发射
Rubicon knows the missiles didn't launch.
所以一直在发送发射代码
It keeps trying to send launch codes.
我们必须一个个手动重写
Which we have to override manually one by one.
有点像打地鼠
It's kind of like whack-a-mole.
但我们赢了并没有毛绒玩具奖励
Except we don't get a stuffed animal if we win.
真的吗
Is it true?
有一枚已经发射了
There's one in the air?
目标直指市政局纪念厅
Headed straight for Monument Point.
你能重写吗
Can you override?
诺亚在那边守着导弹不出仓
That is what I'm trying to do
我这边一直在设法重写
while Noah keeps the missiles in their silos.
我们得开始疏散群众
We need to start evacuations.
已经来不及疏散所有人了
There's not enough time to get everyone out.
我是超能力联合调查组的指挥官莱拉·麦考斯
This is ARGUS Director Lyla Michaels.
现报告一起末日事件
I'm reporting an endtime event.
目标为市政局纪念厅
Target is Monument Point.
费利西蒂
Felicity.
我在试着黑进他们的导航系统
I'm trying to hack their navigation systems.
那是什么
What's that?
我建立的地脉算法得到的结果
Another hit in the ley line algorithm I set up.
我交叉对比了新闻报道
I cross-referenced it with news reports and--
市长办公室刚以气体泄漏为名
The mayor's office just evacuated city hall
疏散了市政厅
due to a gas leak.
像你说的  达克想毁了这城市
Like you said, why would Darhk's wife run
那他的妻子为何还要竞选市长
for mayor of a city he wants to destroy?
为了此刻
To gain access to city hall
能进入市政厅
for this exact moment.
结点室肯定在市政厅下面
The Nexus Chamber must be beneath that building.
他要藏也会藏在能吸收
If he's hiding where he should be hiding
核袭击能量的地方
to absorb the power of a nuke attack.
咱们走
Let's go.
你得改变导弹的路线
You need to divert that missile.
算你走远  我现在忙得没法回呛一句
You are lucky I'm too busy to come up with a witty response
你刚说的话
to that right now.
停下  停下
Stop. Stop! Unh!
泰安娜  你没事吧  受伤了吗
Taiana, are you ok? Are you hurt?
有点不对...
Something's...
大部分搞定了
Got it! Mostly.
-什么  -把剩下的
- What? ?- Sent the remaining
发射算法加载到一个死循环里
launch algorithms into an infinite loop.
大概能给我们争取到一天的时间
Should buy the world 24 hours, give or take.
那枚朝市政局纪念厅发射的导弹怎么办
What about the nuke headed to Monument Point?
锁定了  这些东西被设计成
It's stubborn. There's a reason why these things
锁定路线是有原因的
were designed to be impossible to move off course,
所以我只能把市政局纪念厅挪个地
which is why I have to move Monument Point instead.
GPS重新排列
GPS realignment.
什么意思
What do you mean?
以前为了好玩我重定位了GPS卫星
As a prank, I once relocated a GPS satellite.
在东海岸的人还以为
Everyone on the eastern seaboard
他们的实际位置在以西三千两百多米处
thought they were 20 miles west of their actual location.
扰乱导弹的定位  就可以避免直接击中
Do that to the missile, you avoid a direct hit.
重算坐标
市政局纪念厅
海文洛克
这就行了
That's it.
直接击中海文洛克
Direct hit on Havenrock.
这样死伤最少
Maximum yield.
伤亡情况如何
How many casualties?
好几万
Tens of thousands.
不然市政局纪念厅会有几百万人伤亡  费利西蒂
Monument Point would have been a couple million, Felicity.
该死  我们都搜遍了
Damn it. We searched everywhere.
你好  奥利弗
Hello, Oliver.
来得正好
Nice timing.
你现在需要更大的箭头了
I think you're gonna need much bigger arrows.